gamescene.com 2014-06-20

# CleverMedia: Games and Apps

CleverMedia, Inc., and its advertisers and affiliates are deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. We do not collect information for any marketing purposes at all. No membership or sign-up is required for playing any of the games on our sites.

High Score Board Names: Under our new system, you can submit your score as a guest using any name or alias. No other information is recorded. If you wish, you can sign up for a reserved name, which can be an alias. This means that no one else can use your name or alias on the high score boards from that point on. To do this, you must provide an email address. This is used to email a password to you. it is also used to verify that you have not signed up for a reserved name before -- we want there to be only one reserved name per person. We do not use this email address for any other purpose. We do not resell this email address or use it to send any announcements, newsletters or advertisements. Optionally, you can provide your location from a list of counties and states. This is to allow us to show high score boards sorted by location. It is not used in conjunction with your email address for any other purpose.

Multiplayer Game Names: Users are asked for an alias when they enter a multiplayer game area. This alias is used to identifiy the players in the game. No other information is collected. These aliases are not used for any other purpose.

Recommend to a Friend: When you use the "Recommend this game to a friend" feature on one of our sites, your email address is required so that it can be attached to the email, just like it would be if you were sending an email using client software. We do not use this email address for any other purpose.

Advertisements: CleverMedia, Inc. uses a variety of Web advertising companies. These companies place banner ads and pop-up windows on our site automatically. They each have a privacy policy. You can find the individual ad company policies in links organized by site further down in this document.

CleverMedia, Inc. does not collect email addresses or any other information about our visitors except where specified above.

**COPPA Compliance** :

CleverMedia, Inc. is required by law to provide you with the following information:  

* There is a link to the site's privacy policy (this page) on the home page of each of CleverMedia, Inc. sites. 
* There is a a link to the site's privacy policy on each page where personal information is collected. However, no personal information collected on any of our pages.
* Here is a disclosure of the types of personal information we collect from children and how our site uses that information: We don't collect ANY information from children.
* Here is a disclosure in about whether the personal information we collect from children is shared with third parties, and, if so, how the third parties use the information: We don't collect ANY information from children or anyone else, so we don't have any information to share.
* Here is a disclosure in that parents have the right to review and delete any personal information your site previously collected from their child: We don't collect ANY information from children or anyone else, so we don't have any information that parents can review or delete.
* Here is the contact information for our website operator: [email us](http://clevermedia.com/email-feedback.html). See the bottom of this page for complete contact information.

**Privacy at GameScene and Other Game Sites:**

CleverMedia, Inc.'s sites use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web sites. Our third-party advertising companies also may separately place or recognize cookie files on your browser in the course of delivering advertisements to this Site. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, you can find out more here:

Some ads at our sites are served by Google AdSense. Read their privacy statement at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>.

Some ads at our sites are served by Tribal Fusion. Read their privacy statement at <http://www.tribalfusion.com/TribalFusion/privacy.html>.

Some as at our sites are served by BurstMedia. Read their privacy statement at <http://www.burstmedia.com/isl/privacy.asp>.

In addition, please note:  
_We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies,[click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)._

Some ads at our sites are served by Specific Media. Read their privacy statement at <http://specificmedia.com/privacy.php>.

Some ads at our sites are served by Commission Junction. Read their privacy statement at <http://www.cj.com/privacy.html>.

* * *

**CONTACT INFORMATION**

If you have any further questions, please [contact us](http://clevermedia.com/email.html).

According to law, we must provide complete contact information in our privacy policay. This information is provided for privacy policy issues ONLY. If you use this to SPAM us or send us unsolicited mail or make unsolicited phone calls, we will take appropriate action.

Email address: We have provided a link to a form where you can [email us](http://clevermedia.com/email-feedback.html). Use this form. However, because the law is unclear whether this is enough, we need to provide an email address here. Because SPAM software will search this page, pick up this email address, and SPAM us, we will provide a special email address only for privacy policy inquiries: privacy2(at)clevermedia(dot)com. Notice that I have replaced the @ symbol with (at) and the . with (dot) so that the email can't be harvested by spammers from this page. If anyone uses this special email address to send us SPAM, we will take appropriate action according to federal and state laws.

Mailing address: CleverMedia Inc., 200 W. Hampden Ave. Englewood, CO 80110. Do not send us junk mail.
